http://www.esoprs.com/for-members/user-help-page/

User help pageHomeFor MembersUser help pageForgotten PasswordForgotten passwords can be reset on this pagehttps://www.esoprs.eu/members/login?sendpassAccessing your personal dataOnce you are logged in you can view your user “Dashboard” herehttps://www.esoprs.eu/members/memberThe dashboard has links to the key user areas on the websiteUser ProfileUsers can edit their profile information. Account password can be changed here.Address information is stored here and is passed to the payment gateway to prefill forms prior to payment.https://www.esoprs.eu/members/profileWe have deleted old profile fields that were carried over from previous versions of the site.Subscription PaymentsMembers can pay for annual subscriptions and pay for missing years subscriptions.https://www.esoprs.eu/members/member/add-renewPayment HistoryAll invoices for payments made via the website are stored here (the new website was launched in February 2018). Payments made via the old website are not included in this area.https://www.esoprs.eu/members/member/payment-historyHelpdeskIf you have any questions about the website you can post questions here or emailwebmaster@esoprs.euhttps://www.esoprs.eu/members/helpdeskESOPRS ForumsForums are available for members to discuss whatever they wish. These forums are private to members only. The data stored in your forum profile is copied from the main website profile. IF you are discussing patient data please ensure you get patient consent before posting.https://www.esoprs.eu/forum/Find MembersWebsite visitors can search the website for ESOPRS members who wish to have their details publicly displayed to the public. This is optional. The data used here is stored in a separate area which can be accessed by logged in members only. Click on “create/edit their own profile here” to create or edit your public profile. Members can add as much or as little info as they wish, including a photo. You can also add an email address that can be viewable to other members only, or publicly viewable, or not viewable at all.https://www.esoprs.eu/find-members/ESOPRS ApplicationNon-members, or members that wish to change their membership level can apply from this pagehttps://www.esoprs.eu/esoprs-application/FellowshipsFellowships can be viewed on this pagehttps://www.esoprs.eu/news-papers/european-oculoplastic-orbital-fellowships/Members can add memberships on this pagehttps://www.esoprs.eu/news-papers/add-fellowship/Download Personal DataThe user dashboard contains a link under “Useful Links >> Download Personal Data”  to a page where you can download the personal data we hold on your accounthttps://www.esoprs.eu/members/personal-data/downloadYou can also request further info if you wish to get a report of data you have entered into various forms on the site, eg “application forms”, “fellowship place added”, “public member information” (this is separate information entered by yourself that is viewable to the public) on this pagehttps://www.esoprs.eu/find-members/Removing/Deleting Personal Data and AccountsIf you wish to remove your details from the society and/or the website, please send an email via the helpdesk in your accounthttps://www.esoprs.eu/members/helpdeskor emailwebmaster@esoprs.euUpdated November 2018This page documents the recent updates and on-going work in light of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).We (ESOPRS www.esoprs.eu and website support team at MediSites www.medisites.co.uk) refer to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) website for guidance https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/ and the Official Journal of the European Union for EU regulation https://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/PDF/?uri=CELEX:32016R0679&from=ENGDPR is a practical approach on how to handle all different aspects of data security.GDPR affects any data that could be used to personally identify someone (any EU citizen), eg names, emails, address, etc.The main idea behind GDPR is that users should be granted certain rights over their data.to know what personal data is collected and for how longto know if personal data is shared with third partiesto be able to get/download personal data (data portability)to be able to edit/correct personal datato be able to delete personal dataGDPR applies to all website holding data on EU citizens, so you should be seeing these users rights on most websites that store personal information.Even if you are not an EU citizen, it is a good idea to follow these guidelines as it is common sense and open approach to handling data and keeping users informed on what information is stored, how it is used, and how it can be edited/deleted.You can view the full details of how ESOPRS processes your personal data in our privacy policy here https://www.esoprs.eu/about-esoprs/privacy-policy/ Search for:
Recent News ESOPRS and SASOPS partner societies ESOPRS and AIMO partner societies New ESOPRS Members 2020 ESOPRS AGM 2020 Obituary Prof. Dr. Holger BusseUpcoming EventsDue to the recent COVID-19 pandemic, we can no longer confirm that scheduled events will be happening. Jan 21 2021
Australasian Academy of Facial Plastic Surgery (click title for more info)After the success of our Blepharoplasty and Rhinoplasty meetings, we are proud to announce another outstanding Blepharoplasty conference scheduled for 21 – 23 January, 2021.From around the world, the best of blepharoplasty and facial rejuvenation experts will come together to compare notes on the latest techniques and challenges so we can maintain professional currency, and evolve the art of facial aesthetic surgery as a whole.Download the PDFRead More Apr 14 2021
Conrad Hotel, Seoul, Korea
4th International Orbital Society Symposium in conjunction with the 17th Samsung Oculoplastic Symposium (click title for more info)IOSS 2021Venue: Conrad Hotel City, Country: Seoul, Korea Website: https://www.orbitsymposium2020.org/ Important Dates 1) Deadline for Abstract Submission: Feb 19, 2021 2) Deadline for Early Registration: Mar 15, 2021We are planning to host the 4th International Orbital Society Symposium 2021 (IOSS 2021) in conjunction with the 17th Samsung Oculoplastic Symposium from April 14 to 15, 2021 at the Conrad Hotel, Seoul, Korea.Due to the situation COVID-19 had presented us today, we postponed the symposium from the initial date of May 8-9 to Sep 1-2, 2020, and again to April 14-15, 2021.As an open meeting of the Orbital Society and the first international conference on orbital diseases to be held in Asia, we are looking forward to outstanding and impactful presentations and in-depth discussions. Our program features world-renowned speakers with a wide array of experiences and expertise in clinical topics and research of orbital diseases.We warmly invite you to join us in this global symposium on orbital diseases. You will find this symposium to be an enjoyable opportunity to share your experiences and learn the newest developments and advances in the research.Read More May 07 2021
Barcelona, Spain
Barcelona Oculoplastics (click title for more info)Barcelona Oculoplastics (BOC), to be held at the Instituto de Microcirugía Ocular (IMO), Barcelona, on May 7 and 8, 2021.BOC 2021 will broadcast live oculoplastics surgeries, workshops on aesthetics and rejuvenation, as well as a 3D endoscopy session.The meeting will also feature the participation of eminent international speakers, who will also present advances and techniques through lectures, clinical cases and panel discussions.Information is available at the event’s website www.barcelonaoculoplastics.comWe hope you will find Barcelona Oculoplastics interesting. BOC 2021 Read More Aug 04 2021
Oxford, UK
BOPSS 2021 Annual Meeting (click title for more info)BOPSS 2021, Oxford Wednesday 4th – Friday 6th August 2021 Venue:  Keble College Oxford, UKThe organising committee is delighted to welcome you to Oxford for BOPSS 2021 annual scientific meeting. The meeting will be held from 4th – 6th August 2021 at Keble College, Oxford, situated in the city centre.We are also delighted to welcome our two invited keynote speakers:Dr David Jordan, Ottawa, Canada.Dr Dinesh Selva, Adelaide, Australia.We hope you can join us for what we expect will be a very educational and sociable few days.Jonathan Norris, Tristan McMullan, Manoj ParulekarRead More Sep 16 2021
Naples, Italy
2021, 39th ESOPRS Annual Meeting in Naples, Italy (click title for more info)2021, 39th ESOPRS Annual Meeting in Naples, Italy.The Meeting in Naples will now be scheduled for 16-18 September, 2021.Local organizers: Diego Strianese, Adriana Iuliano, Fausto Tranfa, Giovanni Uccello.Venue: Stazione Marittima.PCO: Sistema Congressi S.R.L.2020.esoprs.euRead MoreESOPRS News
ESOPRS Webinars: Challenging Clinical Cases July 3, 2020
ESOPRS and SASOPS partner societies December 3, 2020
ESOPRS and AIMO partner societies November 30, 2020
New ESOPRS Members 2020 November 2, 2020 ESOPRS AGM 2020 October 14, 2020
Obituary Prof. Dr. Holger Busse September 15, 2020Annual MeetingThe Meeting in Naples will now be scheduled for 16-18 September, 2021.LoginLogin Password
Signup Here Lost Password
Privacy policy - Imprint - GDPR© Copyright 2020. ESOPRS All Rights Reserved.EUROPEAN SOCIETY OF OPHTHALMIC PLASTIC AND RECONSTRUCTIVE SURGERY .Created and managed by MediSites Welcome
to the ESOPRS website, Username/Email
Help pagesThe Meeting in Naples will now be scheduled for 16-18 September, 2021. more info hereHomeAbout ESOPRS About ESOPRSThe SocietyRegulationsCommitteeMembershipAnnual MeetingsLecturersOrbit JournalJunior AwardGrantsUpcoming EventsNews & Events Latest ESOPRS NewsESOPRS 2020 MeetingESOPRS 2020 Winter MeetingUpcoming EventsEuropean Oculoplastic & Orbital FellowshipsNews ArchivesFind MembersFor Patients Medical TerminologiesInformationFor Members ESOPRS 2020 is now 2021 MeetingCase Discussion ForumUser DashboardAdd fellowshipPatient consent formsPartners & LinksContactLog In
